const OD = [
  {
    question: "Which out of the championships in WWE has John Cena never held?",
    answer: "intercontinental championship",
    finisher: "given an Attitude Adjustment by John Cena",   
  },
  {
    question: "Which former member of the shield was the first one to win the intercontinental championship?",
    answer: "dean ambrose",
    finisher: "given a Dirty Deeds by Dean Ambrose",   
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the very first Divas Champion, which she won back in 2008?",
    answer: "michelle mccool",
    finisher: "given a Faith Breaker by Michelle McCool",   
  },
  {
    question: "Which superstar is billed from the bottomless pit?",
    answer: "the boogeyman",
    finisher: "given a Boogey Slam by The Boogeyman",   
  },
  {
    question: "Which superstar won the inaugural Money in the Bank ladder match in 2005?",
    answer: "edge",
    finisher: "given a Spear by Edge",   
  },
  {
    question: "Who holds the record for the longest time in a Royal Rumble match?",
    answer: "rey mysterio",
    finisher: "given a 6-1-9 by Rey Mysterio",   
  },
  {
    question: "Which superstar won the inaugural Andre the Giant Memorial Battle Royal at WrestleMania 30?",
    answer: "cesaro",
    finisher: "given a Neutralizer by Cesaro",   
  },
  {
    question: "Which WWE Hall of Famer was sworn in as the new President of the United States of America?",
    answer: "donald trump",
    finisher: "given a Covfefe by Donald Trump",   
  },
  {
    question: "Who holds the record for most Royal Rumble eliminations?",
    answer: "roman reigns",
    finisher: "given a Superman Punch by Roman Reigns",   
  },
  {
    question: "What rebellious group led by Wade Barrett caused havoc on Raw?",
    answer: "nexus",
    finisher: "given a Wasteland by Wade Barrett",   
  }
];

const AR = Array.from(Array(OD.length).keys());

module.exports.OD = OD;
module.exports.AR = AR;
